A
thousand miles of winter grey Another dawn,
another day The engines hum, a weary soul A heavy
price, a heavy toll I see your face on frozen
glass A man that's built to last A single light
that I must find To leave the endless dark behind
And the lights are bright On this winter's night
Because you're coming home Yes, you're finally
coming home Through the wind and rain Through
the doubt and pain You are not alone No, you're
finally No, you're finally coming
home Jumps down a ladder, about to melt The
reddish spot that melts But no more than a
whispered vow It feels so close, it's coming now
The fire's lit, the table's set A promise that I
haven't met But in my heart, the feeling grows A
warmth that melts the winter snow
And the lights are bright On this winter's night
Because you're coming home Yes, you're finally
coming home Through the wind and rain Through
the doubt and pain You are not alone No, you're
finally coming
you.
And the lights are bright on this winter's night
Because you're coming home Yes, you're finally
coming home Through the wind and rain Through
the doubt and pain You are not alone Know you're
finally coming home
Coming home
On this day